boxoffice.com 2019-11-12

# Privacy Policy - Boxoffice

**Boxofficepro.com – Privacy Policy**

Box Office Media LLC respects your privacy. The very nature of the services Box Office Media LLC provides in support of each customer’s Boxoffice® Magazine or e-newsletter (the “ **Box Office Media LLC Newsletter** ”) focuses on the collection and analysis of various types of information that Box Office Media LLC Newsletters users voluntarily provide us.  Box Office Media LLC recommends that you read this privacy policy (this “ **Policy** ”) so you will understand the information Box Office Media LLC collects, and the manner in which Box Office Media LLC may use such information. Please keep in mind that our commitment to meeting the demands of our users may result in changes or additions to this Policy. Box Office Media LLC may modify or supplement this Policy from time to time. If Box Office Media LLC decides to change this Policy, Box Office Media LLC will post those changes on this page, and your continued use will be subject to such changed Policy.

This Policy describes how Box Office Media LLC collects, uses, and discloses your Personal Information in connection with the use of our websites (“ **Website Services** ”), applications (“ **apps** ”), or other service that refers to or links to the Policy, as well as any offline products, programs and services (collectively our “ **Services** ”).

We want to help you inspire great experiences through movies and entertainment, through our Services. Before you use our Services, please read this Policy in its entirety, which helps you make informed decisions about your relationship with us.

1\. INTRODUCTION

 **Personal Information**. “ **Personal Information** ” is data that relates to you and can — either on its own or in combination with other information — identify you as an individual. Personal Information does not include data that has been aggregated or made anonymous such that you can no longer be identified using any means reasonably available to us.

**Our Services**. The Services referenced in this Policy include the Services provided by Box Office Media LLC (“ **Boxoffice Media** ” or “ **Boxoffice** ® **Pro** ”).

**References to “you”**. In this Policy, “ **you** ” means anyone who uses our Services, websites, or applications.  This Policy explains how we use Personal Information in the context of your use of our Services.  

2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT  

The Personal Information that we collect and how we use that information depend on your relationship with us and the requirements of applicable law as described below.  

We collect information:

  * that you provide to us directly.
  * about your devices and their location, and your use of our Services, including through cookies, and other Internet technologies. 
  * that we obtain from other sources.

**How to Disclose.**  There are several ways you can disclose personal information to us and Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customers, and can be done based on the following:  

  * You will be able to provide information about your interests through email surveys. This information will assist Boxoffice® Pro and Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customers to customize the emails you receive. 
  * If Boxoffice® Pro corresponds with you directly, we may store this correspondence.

**Special Disclosures.**  There are several other features of the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter that require certain additional information in order to use them. The information that you provide for these options will not be used for any reason other than that for which you provide the information.  Whenever Boxoffice® Pro runs a contest or sweepstakes, we will tell you what information we will collect from you, how it will be used, and whether we will share it with anyone, such as a third party sponsoring the contest or sweepstakes or a service provider we utilize to manage the event. 

3\. INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU  

Boxoffice® Pro requests different types of Personal Information from you, depending on the Services you use and your relationship with us. We may collect the following categories of information, depending on the Services that you use:

  * Contact Information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address and other information that enables us to contact you;
  * Professional Information, including your company name, title, role and other information about your profession;
  * Payment Information, including your credit or debit card details, bank account information, and payment or other information required when you make a purchase;
  * Other Personal Information, including details such as the purpose of your visit, and data or files that you input, upload or store with the Services, such as search queries that you submit, and documents that you upload to the Services. 

We will also process personal data included in content and information that you add to your member network or other community profile.

We also collect and store communications, such as e-mail, and any other information you choose to share with us — including your photos and groups with which you are affiliated — and that you send or receive using the Services.  

4\. INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM SOURCES OTHER THAN YOU

**Social Media**. Boxoffice® Pro collects Personal Information to enable you to use any online social media resources, including use of our Website. If you register or log into your account through a third-party social media service, we will have access to some of your third-party account information from that service, such as your name and other information in that account, as authorized in your settings on that service. You have the ability to disable the connection between our Services and your third-party account at any time.  

**Information from Third-Party Sources**.  We may receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources and other third parties as permitted by law. We combine this information with Personal Information or other information that we receive from or about you, where necessary to provide the Services you requested.  

**Google Analytics.** We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of our Website Services (e.g., Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Website Services, what pages they visit, when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website Services). Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date that you visit the Website Services, rather than your name or other identifying information. The information collected through the use of Google Analytics is not combined with your Personal Information.   Learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data and opt-out options at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.  

**Information Used for Interest Based Advertising**. Through the Website Services, we allow third-party advertising partners to set tracking tools (e.g., cookies) to collect anonymous, non-Personal Information regarding your activities (e.g., your IP address or page(s) visited). We also share such information that we have collected with third-party advertising partners. These advertising partners use this information (and similar information collected from other websites) to deliver future advertisements to you when you visit non-Boxoffice-managed websites within their networks. Such advertisements are based on your interests. 

  **Mobile Computing.** We provide websites and online resources that are specifically designed to be compatible and used on mobile computing devices. Mobile versions of the Services require you to log in with an account. In such cases, information about use of each mobile version of the website may be associated with user accounts. In addition, Boxoffice® Pro enables you to download an application, widget or other tool that can be used on mobile or other computing devices. Some of these tools may store information on mobile or other devices. These tools transmit Personal Information to Boxoffice® Pro to enable you to access your user accounts and to enable Boxoffice® Pro to track use of these tools. Some of these tools enable you to e-mail reports and other information from the tool.  

5\. ANONYMOUS AND AGGREGATED INFORMATION  
We also collect and/or generate anonymized and aggregated information from your use of the Services. We may provide aggregate statistics about the members of its customers’ Boxoffice® Pro Newsletters, traffic patterns, read rates, redemption rates, and related site information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes or to third party vendors. We do not supplement the information we collect from members with information from third parties to make member information personally identifiable.  We use anonymized and aggregated information in various ways, including to measure your interest in and use of portions or features of the Services. Anonymized or aggregated information is not Personal Information.  

6\. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  

How we use your Personal Information depends on your relationship with us. In general, we use your Personal Information to:

  * provide you with our Services, in order to meet our contractual obligations to you or your company, keep our systems secure and protect against fraud, abuse or other improper conduct;
  * contact you about our Services, promotions, and sweepstakes. (We generally rely on our legitimate interests in marketing our Services to you, whether on our own websites or on third party websites, and in providing these promotions or sweepstakes, where permitted by applicable law. We work to ensure that we do not use your Personal Information in ways you would not expect by allowing you to opt out of receiving all such communications (unless they are solely related to the provision of our Services to you and have no marketing element) and, where required by applicable law, we will not send any such messages without your prior consent.);
  * comply with our legal obligations.  (Among other things, we use Personal Information to comply with financial reporting obligations, or court orders, warrants, or subpoenas in accordance with applicable law.)
  * improve our products and Services, to better tailor and provide the Services. (IP addresses are used to diagnose problems, administer our website, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the website, and deliver customized, personalized content, or to support our legitimate interests to provide the best Services possible to our users.)

**IP Addresses**.  Boxoffice® Pro uses internet protocol (“ **IP** ”) addresses to analyze trends, administer the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter system, track our users’ movement and web browsers used and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  

**Tracking.**  Boxoffice® Pro automatically tracks certain information, including banners or other hyper-links clicked on and whether members read the email messages from their Boxoffice® Pro Newsletters. This information is provided to respective customer sponsoring the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter and may include personally identifiable information.

**Your Permissions**.  You will receive emails only if you grant us or the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customer permission to communicate the news of the customer to you. You must also provide us or the customer with your name and email address to allow us to communicate a personalized message to you. You can do this by:  

  * completing a Boxoffice® Pro enrollment card to join a customer’s Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter;
  * clicking on the various hyper-links found throughout our pages; or
  * providing your name and email address and granting consent to a customer by some other means;

**Third-Party Materials.**  Emails you receive from us may contain advertisements and links to other websites (“ **Third Party Materials** ”). Boxoffice® Pro is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of these Third Party Materials. This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information Boxoffice® Pro collects from you in connection with the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter system. This Privacy Policy does not govern information Boxoffice® Pro may collect from you on any other website in The Boxoffice Company network, which should be considered Third Party Materials for purposes of this Privacy Policy. Boxoffice® Pro encourages you to be aware that when you visit third party websites or our other websites that you should investigate, inquire about, and review the privacy policies of Third Party Materials before you disclose your personal information.   

**Profile Information.**  You should receive a confirmation of your enrollment in the first Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter you join and when you join additional Boxoffice® Pro Newsletters, your name and email address, and any other general information you have voluntarily provided to us in the “Update Email Settings” section of our website (“ **Profile Information** ”) will be shared with you and added to the member information for the Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter.  Information you voluntarily provide specifically for one customer will not be shared with other customers.   

**Sharing with Subcontractors.** We may employ data entry firms or other service vendors to assist us, and such other vendors will also be subject to confidentiality agreements and will not have any right to use or disclose member information except in connection with their contracted services.  

**Age-Related Information.**  Please note that, although you may, you are under no obligation to provide extra personal information, other than that set forth herein, in order to continue to receive your periodic promotion and special event news; provided however that where customers are required by law to receive additional age related information, this information will be requested of you. 

**Sharing with Other Newsletter Customers.**  Boxoffice® Pro collects and has access to all of the above member information and may share information you provide to us specifically for a Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customer in a form that may link the information with personal information that can identify you, only with that Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customer. The specific Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter customer for whom you are providing the information will own the information. Boxoffice® Pro will share Profile Information you provide and information may be in a personally identifiable form.

**Sale or Transfer.**  Unless otherwise set forth herein, Boxoffice® Pro does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others or share it with others. If the ownership of a customer sponsoring a Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter changes due to the sale of all or substantially all of the assets of the customer or the controlling stock or other ownership interest, the new owner may have the same rights of access and ownership of your personal information as the previous owner. Similarly, if a purchaser acquires substantially all of our assets or stock, the purchaser will succeed to our rights with respect to your personal information.  Boxoffice® Pro will not otherwise sell or share your personal information with third parties unless we first notify you and you permit the transfer. 

**Compliance.**  Boxoffice® Pro will disclose member information as required by law, court order, or as requested by government or law enforcement agencies. Boxoffice® Pro will cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services to further illegal activity. Boxoffice® Pro also reserves the right to report any illegal activity to law enforcement for prosecution.

**Your Rights.**  In certain circumstances — in particular where we use Personal Information on the basis of our legitimate interests or your consent — and where permitted by applicable law, you have the right to object to our uses of your Personal Information.  

7\. CHANGING YOUR MEMBERSHIP TYPE

**Opting Out.** You will have the opportunity to opt out of membership in any Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter whenever you receive an email for that specific Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter.  If you opt out of membership, your name will be added to a list of individuals who have ended their membership and the transmission of emails to you will stop no later than seven business days from your request. Should you subsequently renew your membership in that Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter, your membership will be reinstated as though no break in your membership had occurred. Please note that if you do choose to cancel your membership in a Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter, your information remains in our database, but your membership will be deactivated. (Special rules will apply for the removal of information for children under the age of 13 who are specifically permitted to join a Boxoffice® Pro Newsletter).

Boxoffice® Pro will retain in our files information that you have requested us to remove in some circumstances, such as to, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the terms and conditions of our website. In addition, prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that Boxoffice® Pro backs up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information would be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

8. **** SECURITY

Boxoffice® Pro takes every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Boxoffice® Pro’s employees are informed of our privacy policies when they are hired.  Additionally, Boxoffice® Pro either provides all employees with a hard copy of the policy or sends the policy to them by email when our Privacy Policy is updated.

**  
**All member data Boxoffice® Pro collects is stored on secure servers and protected against unauthorized access. None of this information is stored on the website. The data network is a secure network protected by a firewall and encrypted password protection systems. Only a few employees have access to member personal information stored in our databases. **Boxoffice® Pro also recommends that you do not divulge your email account password to anyone.** This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or you are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent (100%) secure and third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. As a result, while Boxoffice® Pro will strive to protect your personal communications and information, we cannot fully ensure or warrant that your private communications and personal information will not be disclosed to third parties.

9\. CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

If you live in California, you may opt out of having your Personal Information shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes by e-mailing [privacy@boxoffice.com](mailto:privacy@boxoffice.com).  

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a user communicates. There is no industry standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. We currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard is established and accepted, we may revisit our policy on responding to these signals.

California residents who are registered members or users of the Services and are under the age of 18 may be entitled under California law to request and obtain removal of content and information that they themselves post on the Services. You may request such removal by emailing us at [privacy@boxoffice.com](mailto:privacy@boxoffice.com). In your request, please provide a description of the material that you want removed and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material, including your name, email address, year of birth, mailing address (including city, state, and zip code) and the subject line “California Removal Request.” Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the material. For example, materials that you have posted may be republished or reposted by another user or third party.

**  
**10\. FEEDBACK AND CONTACT INFORMATION

Box Office Media LLC appreciates your comments and questions regarding this Policy. If at any time you believe we have violated this Policy or any of your personal information maintained by us is inaccurate, please notify us by Email or letter and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to investigate and, if we deem necessary, correct such violation or inaccuracy. We can be reached via email at: [privacy@boxoffice.com](mailto:privacy@boxoffice.com). 

Copyright © 2019 Box Office Media LLC. All Rights Reserved.
